Guide to the Judith P. Vladeck Papers WAG.177
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Kyriazi II- Lutrecia Gould- TFC-2412: Notes (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi II- Lutrecia Gould- TFC-2412: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi II- Lutrecia Gould- TFC-2412: Exhibits (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Kyriazi II- Lutrecia Gould- TFC-2412: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Kyriazi II- Bonnie F. Williams- TFC-2001: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Kyriazi II- Bonnie F. Williams- TFC-2001: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Kyriazi II- Bonnie F. Williams- TFC-2001: Notes (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Kyriazi II- Bonnie F. Williams- TFC-2001: Application Material (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Kyriazi II- Bonnie F. Williams- TFC-2001: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Kyriazi II- Delores Flowers- BIG-2590: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Kyriazi II- Delores Flowers- BIG-2590: Exhibits (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Kyriazi II- Delores Flowers- BIG-2590: Notes (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Kyriazi II- Delores Flowers- BIG-2590: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Kyriazi II- Delores Flowers- BIG-2590: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Kyriazi II- Delores Flowers- BIG-2590: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Kyriazi II- Evelyn v. Clarke- BIG-2493/1041: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Kyriazi II- Evelyn v. Clarke- BIG-2493/1041: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Kyriazi II- Evelyn v. Clarke- BIG-2493/1041: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Kyriazi II- Evelyn v. Clarke- BIG-2493/1041: Exhibits (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Kyriazi II- Evelyn v. Clarke- BIG-2493/1041: Notes (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Kyriazi II- Evelyn v. Clarke- BIG-2493/1041: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Kyriazi II- Catherine R. Casselli-BH-2029/2586: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Kyriazi II- Catherine R. Casselli-BH-2029/2586: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Kyriazi II- Catherine R. Casselli-BH-2029/2586: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Kyriazi II- Catherine R. Casselli-BH-2029/2586: Notes (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Kyriazi II- Catherine R. Casselli-BH-2029/2586: Exhibits (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Kyriazi II- Catherine R. Casselli-BH-2029/2586: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Kyriazi II- Sally Holliday-TFC-2519: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Kyriazi II- Sally Holliday-TFC-2519: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Kyriazi II- Sally Holliday-TFC-2519: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Kyriazi II- Sally Holliday-TFC-2519: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Kyriazi II- Sally Holliday-TFC-2519: Notes (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Kyriazi II- Sally Holliday-TFC-2519: Exhibits (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Kyriazi II- Cheri Williams- BH-2020: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Kyriazi II- Cheri Williams- BH-2020: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Kyriazi II- Cheri Williams- BH-2020: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Kyriazi II- Cheri Williams- BH-2020: Notes (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Kyriazi II- Cheri Williams- BH-2020: Application Material (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Kyriazi II- Cheri Williams- BH-2020: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Kyriazi II- Maria E. Pereira- BH-2051: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Kyriazi II- Maria E. Pereira- BH-2051: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Kyriazi II- Maria E. Pereira- BH-2051: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Kyriazi II- Maria E. Pereira- BH-2051: Notes (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Kyriazi II- Maria E. Pereira- BH-2051: Application Material (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Kyriazi II- Maria E. Pereira- BH-2051: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Kyriazi II- Annie J. Booker- BIG-2075: Transcript (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Kyriazi II- Annie J. Booker- BIG-2075: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Kyriazi II- Annie J. Booker- BIG-2075: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Kyriazi II- Annie J. Booker- BIG-2075: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Kyriazi II- Annie J. Booker- BIG-2075: Notes (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Kyriazi II- Annie J. Booker- BIG-2075: Application Material (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Kyriazi II- Minnie Hargrove- TFC-2039: Claim form (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Kyriazi II- Minnie Hargrove- TFC-2039: Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Kyriazi II- Minnie Hargrove- TFC-2039: Interrogatories (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Kyriazi II- Minnie Hargrove- TFC-2039: Notes (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Kyriazi II- Minnie Hargrove- TFC-2039: Transcripts (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Kyriazi II- Minnie Hargrove- TFC-2039: Application Material (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Kyriazi II- Rose DAllesandro- BIG-43-G: Exhibits (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Kyriazi Legal Correspondence, Jan-Oct 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Engineers Inventory Sheets- Cleos Organizations (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Western Electric Employee Records (Box 29)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Helen Miller Appeal: Brief of Appellants (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Helen Miller Appeal: Appendix to Brief of Appellants (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Helen Miller Appeal: Extra Copies of Appeal (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Helen Miller Appeal: Extra Copies of Brief (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Objector/Late Filers Structural Part V (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Objector/Late Filer Structural Part IV (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 34-46; Structural XIII, Apr 26-Jun 18, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Objector/Late Filer Structural Part I (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Objector/Late Filer Structural Part II (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Objector/Late Filer Structural Part III (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structural X, Oct 30-Dec 29, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 11-21; Structural XI, Jan 22-Mar 2, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 22-33; Structural XII, Mar 2-Apr 25, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi Plaintiff Class Members Master Index (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: 47-?; Structural XIV, Jul 6-Nov 12, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi Structural Aiii, Appendix to 3rd Mandamus: Appendix to Petition for Writ of Mandamus- Vol. 1,2,3. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Supreme Court October Term 1979; Structural D (Cert. Petition), Oct 1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi- Cleos Individual Case: Miscellaneous O-2d (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi- Cleos Individual Case: Exhibits O-2c (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi- Cleos Individual Case: Extra Legal Papers O-2b (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi- Cleos Individual Case: Trial Transcript O-2a (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Kyriazi- Cleos Individual Case: Extra Copies (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - FRAP Motion (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Attorneys Fees (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - WE Attorneys Documents ~1748 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits to Plaintiffs Brief (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Chamber Speech (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Deposition Summaries: Joe Ramirez/ George Cook/ Donald Procknow/ Thaddeus Szymczak/ James Meenan/ Dale Jones (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - DRR- Western Electric Notes on Files (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Plant Closing Extra Legal (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Status Conference TranscriptsPlant Closing (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - JSL Deposition Summaries (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Plant Closing Publicity (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Signed Protective Orders (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Main Hurdman Materials (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- 10-K Western Electric (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Western Electric Annual Reports (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric- Appeal Docket RE: Plant Closing Appendix & Extra Briefs (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - WE: Answers to Interrogatories ~2153 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Kyriazi Deposition Notes ~1697 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Kyriazi 7-52 PMC Notes (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Business Necessity Research (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - ~1593 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - KY Current (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Antonopoulou (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Analysis of Hiring, 1967-1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Leaving Codes, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Leaving Codes by Year: 1974-1976, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Leaving Codes by Year, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Hiring Cumulative by Year, 1967-1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 36)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 37)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 38)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 39)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 40)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structural/Settlement Material (Box 41)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structurals (Box 42)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Structurals (Box 43)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 44)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 45)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 46)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 47)
  - Kyriazi Objection Card File; 4 Stage II Class Member Files; August 81 Class Member List, Aug 1981 (Box 48)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric; Stage III; Correspondence (Box 49)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 50)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 51)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric: Trial Transcripts (Box 52)
  - Melani Case: R. Krummel (Box 53)
  - Melani Case (Box 54)
  - Melani Case (Box 55)
  - Melani Case: Otelsberg (Box 56)
  - Melani Case: from ALC in 99 (Box 57)
  - Melani Case (Box 58)
  - Melani Case (Box 59)
  - Melani Case (Box 60)
  - Melani Case: Subclass I (Box 61)
  - Melani Case: Subclass I (Box 62)
  - Melani Case: Southgate (Box 63)
  - Melani Case: Otelsberg (Box 64)
  - Melani Case: CUNY Womens Coalition, etc. (Box 65)
  - Melani Case: Subclass I, future salary adjustment, claim decision (Box 66)
  - Melani Case: Subclass I (Box 67)
  - Melani Case (Box 68)
  - Melani Case: Binders (Box 69)
  - Melani Case (Box 70)
  - Melani Case: R. Krummel (Box 71)
  - Melani Case (Box 72)
  - Melani Case: C. Raphael (Box 73)
  - Melani Case (Box 74)
  - Melani Case: B claim file (Box 75)
  - Melani Case: Foster, Hughes (Box 76)
  - Melani Case: Subclass I, Bolga, Crownower (Box 77)
  - Melani Case: Jonah Otelsberg (Box 78)
  - Melani Case: Minno, Sothgate (Box 79)
  - Melani Case (Box 80)
  - Melani Case: Nancy Bogen (Box 81)
  - Melani Case (Box 82)
  - Melani Case: Class Member Forms (S-End) (Box 83)
  - Melani Case: Goldstein, Donon (Box 84)
  - Melani Case: Huggins, Kraus, etc. (Box 85)
  - Melani Case: Comparative Faculty Docs (Box 86)
  - Melani Case: from ALC in 99 (Box 87)
  - Melani Case: Addl (Box 88)
  - Melani Case: Class members (Box 89)
  - Melani Case: Counsel fees (Box 90)
  - Melani Case: McMahon, Green (Box 91)
  - Melani Case: Minno, Southgate (Box 92)
  - Melani Case: Otelsberg (Box 93)
  - Melani Case: Moche, Constance, Mass (Box 94)
  - JPV General (Box 95)
  - Melani Case: Otelsberg (Box 96)
  - Melani Case (Box 97)
  - Melani Case (Box 98)
  - Melani Case: Green, J. (Box 99)
  - Melani Case: Feesm misc. (Box 100)
  - Melani Case: Subclass I (Box 101)
  - Melani Case: Otelsberg (Box 102)
  - Melani Case: Discovery corresp. (Box 103)
  - Melani Case: Subclass III (Box 104)
  - Melani Case: McMahon (Box 105)
  - Melani Case: Misc. subclass docs (Box 106)
  - Melani Case: Subclass I, future salary (Box 107)
  - JPV Personal (Box 108)
  - JPV Personal (Box 109)
  - Melani Case: Jonah, Otelsberg (Box 110)
  - Melani Case (Box 111)
  - Vladeck files (Box 112)
  - Vladeck files (Box 113)
  - Melani Case (Box 114)
  - Melani Case: R. Krummel (Box 115)
  - Melani Case: N. Bogen (Box 116)
  - Melani Case: McMahon, Green, Bogen (Box 117)
  - Melani Case (Box 118)
  - Melani Case: B. Thomas, Central Office (Box 119)
  - Misc. cases (Box 120)
  - Melani Case: Donleavy (Box 121)
  - Melani Case: Parila (Box 122)
  - Melani Case (Box 123)
  - Melani Case: C. Raphael (Box 124)
  - Melani Case: B. Foster (Box 125)
  - Melani Case (Box 126)
  - Melani Case: Rose Marie ?lton (Box 127)
  - Melani Case: Bateman (Box 128)
  - Melani Case: L. Crownower (Box 129)
  - Melani Case: Status Conferences (Box 130)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 131)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 132)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 133)
  - Box 134 Deleted (Box 134)
  - Melani Case (Box 135)
  - Melani Case (Box 136)
  - Melani Case (Box 137)
  - Melani Case (Box 138)
  - Melani Case (Box 139)
  - Melani Case (Box 140)
  - Melani Case (Box 141)
  - Melani Case (Box 142)
  - Melani Case (Box 143)
  - Melani Case (Box 144)
  - Melani Case (Box 145)
  - Melani Case (Box 146)
  - Melani Case (Box 147)
  - Melani Case (Box 148)
  - Melani Case (Box 149)
  - Melani Case (Box 150)
  - Melani Case (Box 151)
  - Melani Case (Box 152)
  - Melani Case (Box 153)
  - Melani Case (Box 154)
  - Melani Case (Box 155)
  - Melani Case (Box 156)
  - Melani Case (Box 157)
  - Melani Case (Box 158)
  - Melani Case? (Box 159)
  - Box 160 Deleted (Box 160)
  - Melani Case (Box 161)
  - Melani Case (Box 162)
  - Melani Case (Box 163)
  - Melani Case (Box 164)
  - Melani Case (Box 165)
  - Melani Case (Box 166)
  - Box 167 Deleted (Box 167)
  - Box 168 Deleted (Box 168)
  - Melani Case (Box 169)
  - Melani Case: Horowitz, Chutzky, Leff, Weiss, etc. (Box 170)
  - Melani Case (Box 171)
  - Melani Case (Box 172)
  - Melani Case (Box 173)
  - Melani Case (Box 174)
  - Melani Case (Box 175)
  - Melani Case (Box 176)
  - Melani Case (Box 177)
  - Melani Case (Box 178)
  - Melani Case (Box 179)
  - Melani Case (Box 180)
  - Melani Case (Box 181)
  - Melani Case (Box 182)
  - Melani Case (Box 183)
  - Melani Case (Box 184)
  - Melani Case (Box 185)
  - Melani Case (Box 186)
  - Melani Case (Box 187)
  - Melani Case (Box 188)
  - Melani Case (Box 189)
  - Melani Case (Box 190)
  - Melani Case (Box 191)
  - Melani Case (Box 192)
  - Melani Case (Box 193)
  - Melani Case (Box 194)
  - Melani Case (Box 195)
  - Melani Case (Box 196)
  - Melani Case (Box 197)
  - Melani Case (Box 198)
  - Melani Case (Box 199)
  - Melani Case (Box 200)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 201)
  - Kyriazi v. Western Electric (Box 202)
  - General? (Box 203)
  - Subclass I, Future Salary Adjustment Claims (Melani?) (Box 204)
  - Melani Case: Jonah (Box 205)
  - JPV General (Box 206)
  - Melani Case (Box 207)